<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PharaSnap</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">PharaSnap need access to android accessibility framework to read text on your screen as well as to identify where the text and image elements are placed on the screen when you tap on them. No personal data is collected and shared to third parties</string>
    <string name="text_hint_default">Text mode. Tap on the text element to capture</string>
    <string name="text_hint_close_overlay">swipe anywhere on screen or tap collapse button to collapse the overlay</string>
    <string name="app_shortcut_short_label">Launch widget</string>
    <string name="app_shortcut_long_label">Launch widget to copy text on screen</string>
    <string name="text_selection_modal_title">Change text selection</string>
    <string name="entry_list_modal_title">Recent items</string>
    <string name="change_text_modal_title">Edit text</string>
    <string name="text_detection_failed_in_text_mode">Could not detect any text. Perhaps try Image mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_enable_alert_description">You must provide PharaSnap access to use Accessibility service to read text and image content on the screen. Go setting and select PharaSnap to enable accessibility service</string>
    <string name="text_detection_failed">Could not detect any text</string>
    <string name="list_empty_text">No entries yet! This your last 20 recent item list. When a text is identified it will be shown here</string>
    <string name="accessibility_requirement_description">
        Please enable accessibility service to read and identify the positions of text elements and image elements on the screen to extract their text content. On the settings page, select this app and enable accessibility permission.
        \nOn accessibility settings go to installed / Downloaded Apps > Select PharaSnap and toggle the switch \'on\' to grant accessibility service.
    </string>
    <string name="accessibility_requirement_description_first_time">
        For PharaSnap to capture and copy text on the screen. It need access to Accessibility service to read text block on screen and as well identify images block are placed on the screen for image-to-text recognition. No personal data is collected and shared to third parties
        \nOn accessibility settings go to installed / Downloaded Apps > Select PharaSnap and toggle the switch \'on\' to grant accessibility service.
    </string>
    <string name="troubleshoot_button_label">Not detecting text? try troubleshoot</string>
    <string name="introduction">PharaSnap can help you copy text on the screen even on places where you don\'t have the facility directly copy text to clipboard. PharaSnap can even capture text on images without ever leaving the app</string>
    <string name="add_tile_description">To make this tool easily accessible to use it is recommended to add the quick settings shortcut in your notification panel. Open your notification panel, in the top section (quick settings panel) then tap to customize the panel and add the shortcut tile provided by this app to the active area. Drag and place it on a convenient place
        \n\nAnother way to open the widget is by long pressing the app launch icon which prompt you open the widget.
    </string>
    <string name="add_tile_requirement">Quick launching from quick settings in notification tiles is the most recommended way to launch/open this tool because it is very quicker and you don\'t switch between apps, simply slide down the notification tile panel and tap the shortcut button</string>
    <string name="capturing_modes_tutorial">When capturing text there are two modes,
        \n1) Text mode where you simply tap on text element on screen to capture (this could be button, label or multiline paragraph).
        \n\n2) Image mode uses text recognition OCR (for now only support latin characters including english) to capture text on images.
        \nWhen switching to Image mode the app request screen capture session in order to visually see the image content on the screen. (Accessibility Service does not project graphical images on the screen for your Android version). Screen capturing would automatically turn off in 7 seconds after you leave Image mode
        \n\nYou can toggle between the two modes on left-most button on the widget.</string>
    <string name="text_copy_tutorial">Once you tap on the text on screen (not drag and select) it would get highlighted and you can select multiple selections at once.
        By default all text from all selected text blocks will be automatically copied to clipboard once you exit or collapse the floating widget. Also you can use text selection editor to only select the required text from the text blocks when you tap on the yellow bar.</string>
    <string name="recent_items_tutorial">You can also view your last copied items in the recent list from the floating widget itself. You can remove individual items or clear the list altogether.</string>
    <string name="developer_note">This is an app developed by single person. If love this app useful I would like to hear your feedback and thoughts.</string>
    <string name="main_menu_list">main menu list</string>
    <string name="tile_label">Capture text</string>
    <string name="walkthrough_page_content">walkthrough_page_content</string>
    <string name="second_troubleshooting_description">During development phase I have experienced text content some apps will not be available to extract like comment text on YouTube app. However after updating that app to latest version might resolve this issue. So if encountered a similar situation please make sure the host app in in latest version.\nIf none works restart the accessibility service by toggling on and off in accessibility settings</string>
    <string name="first_troubleshooting_description">Some app can request some confidential/private pages on the app like igcognito tabs on chrome to be secured and blocks capturing visual contents on the screen which prevents image to text recognition to work. Please make sure content is not placed on secured screen for example like in chrome open the link from igconito tab to normal tab</string>
    <string name="second_troubleshooting_heading">Not detecting text on Normal mode ?</string>
    <string name="first_troubleshooting_heading">Not detecting text on image mode ?</string>
    <string name="troubleshooting_page_header">Troubleshooting</string>
</resources>